paltip.com 2011-11-24

# PalTip - Privacy

It is hereby emphasized that PalTip is not liable for the privacy polices of other websites which our website has links to. The privacy policy here is only valid for this website. 

PalTip makes use of reasonable data security methods which constitute the standard in the internet industry it also updates and/or upgrades it data security methods, from time to time in order to protect the data. As long as the website uses reasonable security measures it will not be liable for hacking and for the transfer of information of yours to third parties due to the hacking. 

The website retains the right to use different reasonable security measures form the stated above, which reflect the standard of the internet industry, 

### ATT

If you are not satisfied from any part of this website or from this privacy declaration your only remedy is to stop using this site. 

This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. You accept this policy when you sign up for or use our services or any other features, technologies or functionalities offered by us on our website or through any other means. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. In addition, if the revised version includes a substantial change, we will provide you with 30 days’ prior notice by posting notice of the change on the "Policy Updates" page of our website. 

When you visit the PalTip website or use PalTip Services, we collect your IP address and standard web log information, such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our website. 

We may collect and store the following personal information:

  * email address, physical contact information
  * additional information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself or if we believe you are violating site policies
  * Information in order to transfer your part of the commission (PayPal account etc). 

We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. 

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to: 

  * provide the services and customer support you request;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; 
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement;
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising; 
  * Tell you about our services.

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. 

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity. 

If you access our site from a shared computer or a computer in an internet café, certain information about you, such as your User ID, activity or reminders from PalTip, may also be visible to other individuals who use the computer after you. 

**We use "cookies"** (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain of our pages to help analyze our web page flow; customize our services, content and advertising; measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. 

### Account Protection 

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your PalTip password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify PalTip and change your password.
